<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Michal Rogowski</title>
    <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Michal Rogowski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 12:23:53 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rogowski.page/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal CV Page</title>
      <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/personal-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 12:23:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogowski.page/posts/personal-page/</guid>
      <description>Given While I was working on my macOS app Exposure Adjustor. I forgot that in order to upload it to the App Store I have to provide a Support URL, Marketing URL and Privacy Policy URL. Till now it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a problem all of the apps that I&amp;rsquo;ve published were done for big companies that already had a website legal notes etc. The Exposure Adjustor allows you to lock the exposure of your camera to make sure that your face is visible even if there is direct sun or window behind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift Memory Management and Performance</title>
      <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/swift-memory-managment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 12:12:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogowski.page/posts/swift-memory-managment/</guid>
      <description>As part of recruitment processes one of the most common questions is: “What is the difference between struct and class”, we usually can hear that class is copied by reference and struct by value. But what does it even mean? Let’s start with general introduction to Memory Management
 What is memory? We can try to imagine memory as array of cells, each cell contains an information. Typically size of this information is one byte (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why sign-in with apple may take you more than 5 minutes and how it works?</title>
      <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/sign-in-with-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 23:33:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogowski.page/posts/sign-in-with-apple/</guid>
      <description>I saw a lot of articles why Sign In With Apple (SIWA) is - great, easy etc. Only few of them were showing how difficult it may be and this is one of those. I will list all articles that I found about other problems at the end of the article. I described it from iOS perspective.
 BTW! If you like my articles please follow me on Twitter Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow as a Professional Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/grow-as-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 16:54:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogowski.page/posts/grow-as-professional/</guid>
      <description>When I stared my journey as an iOS Developer, it was super easy to find things to learn - to be honest it was hard to find things I knew and I felt confident about. Nonetheless after a year or two there came a dangerous moment of routine: my level of knowledge let me do my job and give a phoney 😱 feeling of being a professional.
Luckily for me a wake-up call came when I was talking with some other iOS Developer and he started to talk about things that I should be familiar with - but I didn’t have a clue what he was talking about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://rogowski.page/posts/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 07:41:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rogowski.page/posts/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Michal Rogowski built the Exposure Adjustor app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Michal Rogowski and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
